

PAUL CHELARU



CONTACT

- chelarupaul1@gmail.com
- 52795964
- www.paulchelaru.com
- Følfodvej 266, 1,-3, 2300 København S Denmark

EDUCATION

2014-2017 Colegiul National "Petru Rares" Suceava, RO

AP DEGREE IN MULTIMEDIA DESIGN

2017-Present

KEA - Copenhagen School of Design and Technology, Copenhagen (Denmark)

COMPUTER SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop Adobe XD Lightroom Microsoft Office

SOCIAL

facebook.com/chelaru.paul

© @chelarupaul

ABOUT

I consider myself to be an ambitious, creative, and open-minded person. From my past experiences I learned the value of teamwork and how to be efficient within a group. I see myself as a sociable person and I am motivated by team effort. Additionally, from the books I have read I learned to see situations from different perspectives, how to be motivated, dedicated, to think outside the box and to be determined to overcome my limits in order to accomplish my goals.

EXPERIENCE

LOGISTICS SUPERVISOR

S.C Anemone SRL (local markets), Suceava, RO | Nov 2016 - Jun 2017

- Planned the re-stock process for the market places (talked with the suppliers, chose the needed products, scheduled the shipping)
- Organized all the invoices and maintained the communication with the accountant
- Took care of the maintenance of the equipment at the stores

EVENT PHOTOGRAPHER

Freelancer, Suceava, RO | Apr 2014 - Sep 2016

- Created a small photography brand with an official Facebook page, a photographic style and a divesified portfolio
- Identified the potential clients (individuals, pubs, local events organized by the town council etc.)
- Maintain the communication with the clients, discussing the shooting details and the financial aspects
- Found each shooting concept and the location
- Met the client's needs and preferences for each shooting in part
- Edited the best selection of photos, using my Photoshop and Lightroom skills

ASSISTANT PHOTOGRAPHER

Oana Toma (well-known wedding photographer), Suceava, RO | Jun 2016 - Sep 2016

- Planned ahead all the details of the wedding with Oana Toma (concept of the shooting, decor, locations, photography accessories)
- Organized and assembled the decor during the grooms shooting
- Installed all the photography accessories for the shooting (lights, speed lite flashes, tripods, shutters etc.)
- Took photos of the wedding atmosphere together with Oana
- Administrated the financial aspect on behalf of Oana



CONTACT

chelarupaul1@gmail.com

\$ 52795964

www.paulchelaru.com

Følfodvej 266, 1,-3, 2300 København S Denmark

EDUCATION

2014-2017 Colegiul National "Petru Rares" Suceava, RO

AP DEGREE IN MULTIMEDIA DESIGN

2017-Present

KEA – Copenhagen School of Design and Technology, Copenhagen (Denmark)

COMPUTER SKILLS

Adobe Illustrator Adobe Photoshop Adobe XD Lightroom Microsoft Office

SOCIAL

f facebook.com/chelaru.paul

(c) @chelarupaul

PHOTOGRAPHER

Padrino, Suceava, RO | Jul 2015 - Oct 2015

- Captured the most relevant moments and beautiful portraits from the events organized by Padrino (local pub in Suceava)
- Took care of the entire post-event editing process, using Photoshop and Lightroom
- Administrated the events section of Padrino's official Facebook page and posted all the photos in the shortest amount of time

CORE QUALIFICATIONS

Web Developing
Basic Graphic Design
Client Relations
Space Planning and Utilization

Photography Knowledge
Photo and Video Editing
Operation Monitoring
Management of Financial Resources

PERSONAL SKILLS

MOTHER TONGUE(S): ROMANIAN

Other language(s): English

UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production	
B2	B2	B2	B2	B2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user - B1 and B2: Independent user - C1 and C2: Proficient user Common European Framework of Reference for Languages

VEHICLE LICENCES

Car Driving Licence